Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Charles E. Young. RESTRICTED. 1951-1992. UARC.0653
UCLA Library Special Collections
Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Charles E. Young. RESTRICTED.
1951-1992
UCLA Library Special Collections
University of California, Los Angeles. Office of the Chancellor
UARC.0653
4.4 Linear Feet (11 boxes)
Record Series 653 contains the restricted administrative files of UCLA Chancellor Charles E. Young. Files regard campus administration, instructional units, committees, University Extension, and University-student relations.
Access
Record Series 653 is RESTRICTED and not open for research. STORED OFF-SITE. Advance notice required. For access, contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9934668093606533
Scope and Content
Record Series 653 contains the restricted administrative files of UCLA Chancellor Charles E. Young. Files regard campus administration, instructional units, committees, University Extension, and University-student relations.
No box 4 exists.
This is an inactive record series; no additional University records are expected to be added.
Record Series 653 is restricted. To view the container list for this collection, please contact UCLA University Archives.
- University Advisory Committee on Investor Responsibility., 1986. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  General
  Index number: A34/U5
- Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Cabinet., 1983-1984. (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
  Index number: DA10
- Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Cabinet., 1969-1981. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Intramural Relations-Student Disruptions., 1970 May. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Index number: HA40 5/70.
- Intramural Relations-Student Disruptions., 1972 May. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Index number: HA40 5/72.
- Student Services-Graduate Division - Min. Recruit.-Bakke., 1974. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Index number: RC31/B3.
- Instructional units-prog. Review-Life Sciences., 1971. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Index: V10/Lsci.
- Org. Research-Prop. Units-Center Study Violence., 1973. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Index: X10/V5.
- Public Svc.-Univ. Extension-Part-time MBA., 1973. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Index: YB1/E8-MBA.
- Office of the general counsel - legal opinions regarding implementation of the regents' divestment policy., 1987 Sep 08. (Box 2)
- The Regents of the University of California - Implementation of the July 1986 Resolution on Divestment - Further Legal Analysis., 1987 Sep 11. (Box 2)
- Index 13. Summary of investment advice regarding divestment presented to regents. 14. Summary of expert witness testimony in board of trustees of the employees' retirement system of the city of Baltimore v. mayor and city council of Baltimore., 1985 Jan-1986 Nov.; Plain blue binder. (Box 2)
- A34/56 - Board of regents - officers - treasurer - investments in South Africa - sealed., 1986. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  South Africa demonstrations and legal issues related to divestment.
- A34/56 - Board of regents - officers - treasurer - investments in South Africa - sealed., 1985. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  conference notes.
- B58 - Systemwide administration/academic affairs/library plans and policies - sealed., 1978. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Correspondence.
- B833/54J Systemwide administrative and academic senate - administrative action - discrimination on the basis of sex - governmental relations., 1975-1976. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  filed complaints and study on the role of UCLA women students in sports activities.
- BD43/A5 - Systemwide administration - business and finance - coordinator of information systems - alumni and development - sealed., 1977. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- DA/U5M4 Campus administration and Los Angeles division academic senate - chancellor's office - chancellor's administrative and advisory committees - university policies - meetings (m4) membership (m5); judicial review committee; registration fee advisory committee (u8)., 1977-1982. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Includes DA16/U5M4, DA16/U5M5, DA16/U5R4, DA16/U5U8.
- HC16 - Intramural relations - faculty discipline - integrity of instructional program - sealed., 1970. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- RF19 Student services and activities - intercollegiate athletics - national collegiate athletic association - investigation of student athletes., 1971-1972. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Investigation of student athletes.
- X33/CbR4-J - Organized research and museums - other organized research programs - international studies and overseas programs - relationships with international organizations - Japan - sealed., 1981-1984. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Japanese exchange program notes and memos.
- Y43/C4 - Public service - overseas programs - Chile/University of California cooperative program - sealed., 1974. (Box 2, Folder 12)
- YB19.1 Public service - university extension - learning resources center - general., 1975-1978. (Box 2, Box 13)
  Establishment of OLRI search for director.
- DA16/A29 Campus Administration and Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Office - Chancellor's Administrative and Advisory Committees - Administrative Affairs Council., 1977-1980. (Box 3, Folder 1-6)
  Meeting minutes.
- FDM - HENAC (Humanistic and Education Needs of the Academic Community) Sealed., 1970. (Box 5)
  HENAC final report.
- Administrative files of Franklin D. Murphy - Sealed., 1951; 1960; 1962-1963. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, report to regents committee on educational policy, newspaper clippings.
- Administrative files of Franklin D. Murphy - Sealed., 1962; 1965; 1968-1970. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Correspondence and summons.
- Administrative files of Franklin D. Murphy - sealed., 1966-1967. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Report to the Los Angeles Division of the Academic Senate of the Committee on University Welfare.
- Administrative files of Franklin D. Murphy., 1965; 1969. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Instructional Units - SEAS - buildings, space and equipment - Thomas Hicks Nuclear Reactor Facility (license renewal)., 1968-1981. (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
  Index: VE2/N8.
- Instructional Units - SEAS - buildings, space and equipment - Thomas Hicks Nuclear Reactor Facility (license renewal)., 1981-1982. (Box 7, Folder 1-5)
- Instructional Units - SEAS - buildings, space and equipment - Thomas Hicks Nuclear Reactor Facility (license renewal)., 1982-1983. (Box 8, Folder 1-5)
- Instructional Units - SEAS - buildings, space and equipment - Thomas Hicks Nuclear Reactor Facility (license renewal)., 1983. (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
- Instructional Units - SEAS - buildings, space and equipment - Thomas Hicks Nuclear Reactor Facility (license renewal)., 1983-1984. (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
- Instructional Units - SEAS -buildings, space and equipment - Thomas Hicks Nuclear Reactor Facility (UCLA Reactor & Olympic Games)., 1984. (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Instructional Units - SEAS - buildings, space and equipment - Thomas Hicks Nuclear Reactor Facility (decommissioning of UCLA Nuclear Reactor)., 1984-1985. (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
- Instructional Units - SEAS - buildings, space and equipment - Thomas Hicks Nuclear Reactor Facility (decommissioning of UCLA Nuclear Reactor)., 1990-1992. (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Instructional Units - SEAS - buildings, space and equipment - Thomas Hicks Nuclear Reactor Facility (license renewal)., 1984-1986. (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Instructional Units - SEAS - buildings, space and equipment - Thomas Hicks Nuclear Reactor Facility., 1980-1982. (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Instructional Units - SEAS - buildings, space and equipment - Thomas Hicks Nuclear Reactor Facility (decommissioning of UCLA Nuclear Reactor)., 1985-1992. (Box 12, Folder 3-5)